Guide to the Earl Casey Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
Earl Casey Accessions
1964-1990
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Casey, Earl
UPWC.21094
2 Linear Feet
4 boxes Audio and digital files on cassette tapes and thumb drives
This collection consists of research documents and taped interviews with transcipts conducted with Jerry Jeff Walker, Walker's family, friends and other musicians. Materials were compiled by Earl Casey as research for the book Gypsy Songman.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research excluding Box 3664-NOTE: BOX 3664 FOLDER 1 IS RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035 WITHOUT CURATOR OR DIRECTOR'S PERMISSION.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Earl Casey 2021
Biographical Notes
Earl Casey is a journalist, former CNN senior vice president and longtime close friend of Jerry Jeff and Susan Walker. Casey served as the chief researcher and writer/consultant on Jerry Jeff Walker's autobiograpy, Gypsy Songman, 1999.
Scope and Contents
Archival materials received from journalist and former CNN senior vice president, Earl Casey. Casey, a longtime friend of Jerry Jeff and Susan Walker, served as the chief researcher and writer/consultant on Jerry Jeff Walker's autobiograpy, Gypsy Songman, 1999. The bulk of the material in this collection dates 1964-1990 and consists of research documents and taped interviews with transcipts conducted with Jerry Jeff Walker, Walker's family, friends and other musicians for the book Gypsy Songman. Research documents include photocopies of Walker's arrest records for his infamous, 1964 New Orleans public intoxication charge, correspondence between Walker, his family and friends, newspaper clippings pertaining to Walker's childhood in Oneonta, New York and his subsequent musical career, a PhD dissertation pertaining to the songs of Jerry Jeff Walker, photographs, drawings, partial draft manuscript for Letters from the Road (original working title for Gypsy Songman) and a copy of Ben Jennings' unpublished memoir. Color coded stickers on cassette tapes and transcripts along with color coded spreadsheet reflect Casey's original numbering system. Folder titles preceding a semicolon reflect Casey's original descriptions. NOTE: BOX 3664 FOLDER 1 IS RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035 WITHOUT CURATOR OR DIRECTOR'S PERMISSION.
Related Materials
The Wittliff Collections also holds the Jerry Jeff Walker collection (TMC 047) as well as the following accessions relating to Jerry Jeff Walker within the Texas Music Collection - 2021 -064,2021-056, 2021-090, 2021-091
Index Terms
Subjects
Guitarists; Guitar music (Folk-rock); Musicians -- Texas; Country music; Composers--Texas; Singers
Subjects (Persons)
Walker, Jerry Jeff
- Accession 2021-094, 2 Linear Feet; 4 boxes Audio and digital files on cassette tapes and thumb drives; Archival materials received from journalist and former CNN senior vice president, Earl Casey. Casey, a longtime friend of Jerry Jeff and Susan Walker, served as the chief researcher and writer/consultant on Jerry Jeff Walker's autobiograpy, Gypsy Songman, 1999. The bulk of the material in this collection dates 1964-1990 and consists of research documents and taped interviews with transcipts conducted with Jerry Jeff Walker, Walker's family, friends and other musicians for the book Gypsy Songman. Research documents include photocopies of Walker's arrest records for his infamous, 1964 New Orleans public intoxication charge, correspondence between Walker, his family and friends, newspaper clippings pertaining to Walker's childhood in Oneonta, New York and his subsequent musical career, a PhD dissertation pertaining to the songs of Jerry Jeff Walker, photographs, drawings, partial draft manuscript for Letters from the Road (original working title for Gypsy Songman) and a copy of Ben Jennings' unpublished memoir. Color coded stickers on cassette tapes and transcripts along with color coded spreadsheet reflect Casey's original numbering system. Folder titles preceding a semicolon reflect Casey's original descriptions. NOTE: BOX 3664 FOLDER 1 IS RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035 WITHOUT CURATOR OR DIRECTOR'S PERMISSION.
  - "Jerry Jeff Walker-New Orleans Police Arrest Blotters 1964-1965 (File N.O. Public Library) -Photocopy: Arrest Index Cards 1964-1965"; Photocopies of New Orleans, LA Police arrest blotters and index cards for Jerry Jeff Walker's Public Drunkenness charge, letter to Earl Casey from Wayne Everard, Archivist, New Orleans Public Library, 1964-1965, 1992 (Box 3661, Folder 1)
  - "Jerry Jeff Walker Letters: jack Frazier/'60's New Orleans: Harry Stoneback (Stoney) Photo: Ryder Coffee House"; Photograph of the Ryder Coffee House, New Orleans, LA with note to Earl Casey from Jack Frazier on back, letter to Casey from H.R. "Stoney" Stoneback regarding Jerry Jeff Walker's birthday concert, letters to Jerry Jeff Walker and Earl Casey from Jack Frazier regarding 1960's New Orleans and the Ryder Coffee House, letter to Pierre De Gruy, editor of Gambit regarding early 1960's New Orleans and the Ryder Coffee House/Lee Harvey Oswald connection, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 3661, Folder 2)
  - "Jerry Jeff Walker Oneonta Newspaper, Library Clippings"; Newspaper clippings from Binghamton Press, The Daily Star and The Oneonta Star newspapers, Oneonta, New York, with stories of Jerry Jeff Walker's (Ron Crosby) Oneonta High School basketball team, The Chymes recording contract, Clyde Conrow's death, Oneonta High School yearbook pages and photocopies of family photographs, 1962, 1965, 1987, 1995, undated (Box 3661)
  - "Photos - AP Wide World 1962 Ft. Lauderdale-others"; Anne Edwards 35mm color slides (5) of Jerry Jeff Walker on railroad tracks in Oneonta, Jerry Jeff Walker Spring Break Ft. Lauderdale B/W 8x10 photograph 4x6 reprint of Jerry Jeff Walker's mother in Oneonta singing group, photocopies of Fayetteville, Arkansas High School yearbook- Jerry Jeff Walkers first professional gig, Faces of Austin brochure, Texas Monthly magazine -Jerry Jeff Walker cover, pg. 78, People magazine - Jerry Jeff Walker and family, pg. 81, 1962, 1965, 1987, 1995, undated (Box 3661, Folder 4)
  - "Jerry Jeff Walker Jerry Jeff Draft Chapter For Autobiography"; Handwritten draft, undated (Box 3661, Folder 5)
  - "Jerry Jeff Walker Burton's Book of Blues - Photos of JJW at Armadillo 1971"; 3 B/W, 8x10 Burt Wilson photographs of Jerry Jeff Walker at the Armadillo World Headquarters, Austin, Texas, letter to Earl Casey from Burton Wilson, piece written by Wilson pertaining to Casey's research for Jerry Jeff Walker book, printout on Wilson's obituary, photocopies of articles on Burton Wilson and the 1970's Austin music scene, 1 copy of Burton's Book of the Blues, signed and inscribed by Burton Wilson, 1971, 1977, 1988, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 6)
  - "Jerry Jeff Walker Ben Jennings Sketches Letters and Some Other "Art" Notes"; Pencil and pen and ink sketches of Jerry Jeff Walker by Ben Jennings, correspondence between Earl Casey and Ben Jennings, 1990, 1999, undated (Box 3661, Folder 7)
  - "Jerry Jeff Walker Rafe Blaugrund -Clippings-Dissertation (USB Drive)"; The Country Road to the Unconscious: Early Childhood Conflict in the Songs of Jerry Jeff Walker, dissertation by Rafe Blaugrund, email to Earl Casey from Katy Tucker, Librarian, Union Institute & University, Cincinnati, Ohio, notes, letter to Susan and JJW from Earl Casey regarding Blaugrund's research, photocopies of newspaper clippings pertaining to JJW, USB drive. File 1 of 2, 1969-1993 (Box 3661, Folder 8)
  - "Jerry Jeff Walker Rafe Blaugrund Clippings"; Photocopies of newspaper clippings pertaining to JJW-research for Blaugrund's dissertation on JJW, The Country Road to the Unconscious: Early Childhood Conflict in the Songs of Jerry Jeff Walker. File 2 of 2, 1985-1992 (Box 3661, Folder 9)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #1- "Oneonta, New York Norma, Jesse, Mel Alma, Cheryl, June 27, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 10)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #2- Alma Crosby and Tony Drago, Oneonta, New York, June 27, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 11)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #3 & 4- Mel Crosby, Oneonta, New York, June 27, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 12)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #5- Jesse Mel, Alma, Oneonta, New York. Photos reviewed by family, providing info, June 27, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 13)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #6- Charles Belden and Jesse Conrow, Oneonta New York., June 27, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 14)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #7- Nicky Lambros, Bob Terrell, The Rail, Jimmy Mosca, Oneonta, New York, June 27, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 15)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #8- Mike Patton by telephone, Glendale, Arizona, October 3, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 16)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #9- Howie Clark by telephone, Johnson City, New York, July 4, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 17)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #10- Ottenheimer. Harriet and Martin Ottenheimer by telephone, Manhattan Kansas, Kansas, University., June 24, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 18)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #11- Dr. Jay Edwards by telephone, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, July 17, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 19)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #11- Marc Ryan by telephone, North San Juan, California, July 17, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 20)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #14-16- Barbara Lyons (Herman), July 12, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 21)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #17- Linda Burris, August 1, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 22)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #18- New Orleans Police Interviews. John Marchese, Willie Patin, Chief Charles Ladell, Frank Wilson, August 3, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 23)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #19-22- Ben Jennings, November 12, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 24)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #23-24- Jerry Jeff Walker and Donny Brooks, April 15, 1987 (Box 3661, Folder 25)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #25- Segle Fry, September 6, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 26)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #26- Allen Damron, September 6, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 27)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #27- Guy Clark and Townes Van Zandt, May 16, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 28)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #28- Gary White, May 1, 1987 (Box 3661, Folder 29)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #29-30- Bob Bruno, March 12, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 30)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #31- Dave Sherstrom, September 7, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 31)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #32-33- Kat Walker, July 22, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 32)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #34- David Bromberg, September 17, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 33)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #35-36- Nick Holmes, July 18, 1987 (Box 3661, Folder 34)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #36-38- Bob Fass, July 18, 1987 (Box 3661, Folder 35)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #39- Paul Sieble, September 6, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 36)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #40- Pat Kenny, September 11, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 37)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #41- Dan Elliot, September 13, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 38)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #42-43- Sally Ann Mitchell, September 9, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 39)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #44- Rod Kennedy, August 22, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 40)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #45- Ramblin' Jack Elliot, March 18, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 41)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #46- Jay Verhultz, August 9, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 42)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #47- Pat Verhultz, August 22, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 43)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #48- Michael M. Murphy and Jerry Jeff Walker, December 30, 1987 (Box 3661, Folder 44)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #49- Michael M. Murphy, December 30, 1987 (Box 3661, Folder 45)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #51- Gary P. Nunn, December 17, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 46)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #52- Craig Hills, August 24, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 47)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #53- John Inmon, December 16, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 48)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Lost Transcript, notes only - Bob Livingston, lost tape #53B, March 17, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 49)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #54- Freddy KRC, August 20, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 50)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #55- Eddie Wilson, August 22, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 51)
  - "Transcripts Family Friends Musicians"; Transcript of taped interview #56- Steve Fromholtz, December 15, 1988 (Box 3661, Folder 52)
  - "Rough Transcripts of Conversations with Jerry Jeff Walker"; Transcripts corresponding to Jerry Jeff Walker interview tapes 05B & 06, 09-13 15, 17-20, 21, 23-27, 001, 003, 004, 1985, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 3661, Folder 53)
  - "1967 Letters From Jerry Jeff To His Parents and Grandparents (Photocopies)"; Photocopies of letters from JJW to his family (Box 3661, Folder 54)
  - "Transcript: < '78/80 Dave Hall (Dawn McAuldy, New Mexico"; Transcript of Jerry Jeff Walker's conversation with Doug Kent Hall pertaining to making a movie based on JJW's life, circa 1978, 1980 (Box 3661, Folder 55)
  - "JJW Tapes. Transcripts"; SanDisk thumb drive marked "JJW". MP3 and PDF files of several audio recordings and transcripts, undated (Box 3661, Folder 56)
  - Letters from the Road by Jerry Jeff Walker. Photocopy of original draft of the first half of book, pp. 10274m 1-10. Letters from the Road is the original working title for Gypsy Songman by Jerry Jeff Walker, published 1999, undated (Box 3661, Folder 57)
  - Audio Cassettes
    - Interview "Oneonta Memory 1 and 2 12-15 yrs"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about his early childhood through junior high school, Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, January 20, 1990 (Box 3662, Item 01)
    - Interview "Oneonta Memory 1 and 2 12-15 yrs"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about his early childhood through junior high school. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, January 20, 1990 (Box 3662, Item 02)
    - Interview "Oneonta Memory 1/21/90 JJW"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about National Guard, bar tending, Kirby Walker, 1962 disappears Florida, New Orleans, Jerry Ferris, persona and Bojangles, Side A. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, January 20, 1990 (Box 3662, Item 05)
    - Interview "Oneonta Memory 1/21/90 JJW"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about National Guard, bar tending, Kirby Walker, 1962 disappears Florida, New Orleans, Jerry Ferris, persona and Bojangles, Side A. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, January 20, 1990 (Box 3662, Item 05b)
    - Interview "Oneonta Memory 1/21/90 JJW"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about National Guard, bar tending, Kirby Walker, 1962 disappears Florida, New Orleans, Jerry Ferris, persona and Bojangles, Side B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, January 20, 1990 (Box 3662, Item 06)
    - Interview "A Drive Around St. Simon 11-15-87"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about original Bojangles lockup photo Key West, Café du Monde, chocolate, alcohol and writing, Side A. Maxell XLII 60 cassette tape, November 15, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 09)
    - Interview "A Drive Around St. Simon 11-15-87"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about original Bojangles lockup photo Key West, Café du Monde, chocolate, alcohol and writing, Side B. Maxell XLII 60 cassette tape, November 15, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 10)
    - Interview "Sea Palms"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about Danny Britt, Lane Bybee George Burns/Bojangles, Bojangles "with little boy eyes", Ben and reading, Side A. Maxell XLII 60 cassette tape, November 15, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 11)
    - Interview "Sea Palms"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about Danny Britt, Lane Bybee George Burns/Bojangles, Bojangles "with little boy eyes", Ben and reading, Side B. Maxell XLII 60 cassette tape, November 15, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 12)
    - Interview "Night Golf In The Headwaters"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about Dark putting green at night and car headlights, Side A, Side B blank. Memorex HB II 90 cassette tape, November 15, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 13)
    - Interview "Ojo Caliente, N.M. 12-29-87 w/ JJW and Susan"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about Rubyiats Dallas '63-64, Troutner to Houston, Side 1, Side 2 blank. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, December 29, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 15)
    - Interview "Drinking Harps in Taos"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about how they drink the wine, poet in New Orleans Golf, St. Andrews and alternative to coke, Side A. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, December 27, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 17)
    - Interview "Drinking Harps in Taos"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about how they drink the wine, poet in New Orleans Golf, St. Andrews and alternative to coke, Side B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, December 27, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 18)
    - Interview "Drinking Harps in Taos"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about freedom screed, HS basketball, friends, Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, side 1, December 27, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 19)
    - Interview "Drinking Harps in Taos"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about freedom screed, HS basketball, friends, Side A. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, side 2, December 27, 1987 (Box 3662, Item 20)
    - Interview "JJW: In New Orleans/JJW NYC CNN"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about New Orleans Larry L. King interview, Side A. Maxell XLII60 cassette tape, 1985 (Box 3662, Item 21)
    - Interview "JJW: In New Orleans/JJW NYC CNN"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about New York after Lone Star Café show, CNN raw, Side B. Maxell XLII60 cassette tape, November 25, 1985 (Box 3662, Item 22)
    - Interview "JJW Atlanta 10-24-88 #1 #2"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about Yankees on radio, Flying Punzars in Austin, Side A. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, October 24, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 23)
    - Interview "JJW Atlanta 10-24-88 #1 #2"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about Pizzarinas, Castle Creek fell-into-drumset story, Side B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, October 24, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 24)
    - Interview "JJW Atlanta 10-24-88 #3 #4"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about JJW Buffett, beer talk Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, side 1, October 24, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 25)
    - Interview "JJW Atlanta 10-24-88 #3 #4"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about writing book, titles, making music philosophy, Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, side 2, October 24, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 26)
    - Interview "JJW Atlanta 10-24-88 #5"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about becoming JJW. "A character…not just musician", Side A, Side B blank. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, October 24, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 27)
    - Interview "Clyde's Farm Austin 1-13-90"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about Oneonta farm, Grandpa Clyde, pony, Side A, Side B blank. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, January 13, 1990 (Box 3662, Item 001)
    - Interview "1-13-90 Clyde #2 JJW about/Guitar Music"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about Clyde, a chaw, a beer, Yankees radio, Side A. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, January 13, 1990 (Box 3662, Item 003)
    - Interview "1-13-90 Clyde #2 JJW about/Guitar Music"; Jerry Jeff Walker talking about Clyde, Jessie, farm, 1956 Yankees fame hookie, Side B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, January 13, 1990 (Box 3662, Item 004)
    - "1-6-98 JJW-Early Oneonta Reworks"; Side A, Side B blank, January 6, 1998 (Box 3662, Item 005)
    - Interview "Oneonta: Norma, Jesse, Mel, Alma, Cheryl, Side A and B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, June 7, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 1)
    - Interview "Oneonta: Alma Crosby Tony Drago"; Alma Crosby (Jerry Jeff Walker's mother) side A, Tony Drago (Jerry Jeff Walker's high school basketball coach), Side B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, June 7, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 2)
    - Interview "Oneonta: Mel: Car Talks"; Mel Crosby (Jerry Jeff Walker's father) Side A and B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, June 7, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 3)
    - Interview "Oneonta: Mel Final Tape 3 Min Only"; Mel Crosby (Jerry Jeff Walker's father) Side A, Side B blank. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, June 7, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 4)
    - Interview "Oneonta: Photo Albums Jesse's Serenade"; Photos reviewed by family, side A, Grandma jessie age 93 plays upright piano, Side B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, June 7, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 5)
    - Interview "Oneonta: -Charles Beldon -Jesse Conrow"; Charles Beldon (Jerry Jeff Walker's high school principal, Side A, Jesse Conrow (Jerry Jeff Walker's grandmother, Clyde's widow), Side B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, June 7, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 6)
    - Interview "Oneonta Nicky Lambros, Bob Terrell, The Rail: Bar, Jimmy Mosca"; Lambros and Terrell Side A, The Rail and Mosca Side B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, June 7, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 7)
    - Interview "Mike Patton 10/2/1988"; Jerry Jeff Walker's teen friend who was on hay wagon the evening JJW's grandfather, Clyde was killed, Side A, Side B blank. Sony UX 90 cassette tape, October 2, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 8)
    - Interview "Howie Clark 7/4/88" Howie led Jerry Jeff Walker on his first runaway from Oneonta, Side A, Side B blank. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, July 4, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 9)
    - Interview "Linda Burris 8/1/90"; Linda Burris girlfriend, Ben, early "Bojangles" memory, married Marc Ryan, Side A and B. Sony UX 90 cassette tape, August 1, 1990 (Box 3662, Item 17)
    - Interview "Ben Jennings -1"; Jerry Jeff Walker's closest friend NOLA, "The Angel" (Kat at taping), Side A I, Side B II. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, November 12, 1988 (Box 3662, Item 19)
    - Interview "Ben Jennings - 2"; Jerry Jeff Walker's closest friend NOLA, "The Angel" (Kat at taping), Side A III, Side B IV. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, November 12, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 20)
    - Interview "Ben Jennings - 3"; Jerry Jeff Walker's closest friend NOLA, "The Angel" (Kat at taping), Side A V, Side B VI. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, November 12, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 21)
    - Interview "Donny Brooks and JJW NYC 2"; Met in Dallas 1965 in winter. Donny, harmonica, Side 1, Side 2 blank. Panasonic 90EN cassette tape, April 15, 1987 (Box 3663, Item 23)
    - Interview "Donny Brooks and JJW NYC 1"; Met in Dallas 1965 in winter. Donny, harmonica, Side A, Side B blank. Panasonic 90EN cassette tape, April 15, 1987 (Box 3663, Item 24)
    - Interview "Segle Fry 9/6/90"; Met Jerry Jeff Walker in Dallas, spring 1965 at the Rubyiant. Austin, Houston, Side A, Side B blank. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, September 6, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 25)